# **JEFF JOYE**

**Web Designer & Developer** 



## **ABOUT**

A dedicated and passionate individual with 9+ years' experience, a keen eye for design, and believes in working in a professional, as well as fun, environment. When I am not working on the computer, I enjoy sports (basketball & outdoor), art (fine & graphic), and music (guitar & vinyl records).



### **CONTACT**



(204) 619-2502



jeffljoye@gmail.com



LinkedIn



Online Portfolio



## **SKILLS**



Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Dreamweaver

InVision Typography

GitHub

SEO

Project Management

Time Management

Communication



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Software Developer, Priceline Partner Network** Winnipeg, MB July 2012 - July 2020

Full-time employee of major travel organization.

- Developed high-quality websites using HTML/CSS and TWIG and maintained functions built from PHP and React.
- Possess strong organizational and analytical skills to successfully manage and prioritize multiple projects.
- Interacted between fellow developers and managers to discuss client requirements and adjust plans as required.
- Displayed ongoing proactivity and dedication by supporting other team members with their workload, often researching and learning new languages and functions.

#### Web Manager, Warehouse One March 2011 - June 2012 Winnipeg, MB

Contract work with branding retail corporate office.

- Maintained the company's website with new products and ongoing promotions to ensure timely implementation.
- Designed web promotional banners and editing product photos.
- Built effective relations with various stakeholders, increasing efficiency via enhanced understanding of each other's needs.
- Used exceptional attention to detail to consistently ensure that the information added to the site was complete and accurate.



## **EDUCATION**

## **Graduate of Web Design Program, Assiniboine Community College**

Brandon, MB

**September 2008 - June 2010** 



# **REFERENCES**

# **Ryan Bend**

**Software Developer/ Scrum Master Priceline Partner Network** 

ryan.bend@priceline.com (204) 962-8094

## **Karl Ginter**

Vice President, **Operations and Product Development Priceline Partner Network** karl.ginter@priceline.com

(204) 795-0234

## **David Jones**

**Principle & Certified Financial Planner Lewis & Jones Group** 

david.jones@investdfsi.ca (204) 523-2708